



Nicolás Meseguer Iborra

DATE OF BIRTH: 18/10/1997

CONTACT

Nationality: Spanish

Gender: Male

Juan de la Cierva, null Murcia, Spain



(+34) 616852360

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ nicolasmeseguer/

ABOUT ME

My name is Nicolás Meseguer, after having studied a higher degree and having done an internship abroad for 6 months, the ambition to learn more about computers made me return to Spain; this time to study computer science. Four years later and with a lot of knowledge behind me, I am still looking for new challenges.

WORK EXPERIENCE

01/02/2021 - 01/06/2021 - Murcia, Spain

Research Initiation Grant

Universidad Católica de San Antonio de Murcia

I was in charge of developing a hybrid hardware accelerator (CPU+GPU) for a recommendation neural network model (DLRM, WATEROT) using specialized accelerator architectures for inference (SIGMA, MAERI). Aiming at maximizing the model efficiency, waiting times and studying memory accesses (W/R) and total cycles consumed

01/03/2018 - 09/09/2018 - Berlin, Germany

Full stack Web Developer

Plinga GmbH

I had the chance to work in an IT company that publishes browser games to millions of active users. I acquired first-hand experience while working on the front-end and back-end of various PHP and Ruby projects, while also managing various services with Amazon AWS, like EC2 servers, databases and CDNs.

Berlin, Germany

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/09/2021 - 01/07/2022 - Murcia, Spain

MSc on New Technologies in Computer Science

Universidad de Murcia

The general objective of the Master's Degree in New Technologies in Computer Science is to train students for research, development and innovation in the area of Information and Communication Technologies, having a clear awareness of its human, economic, legal and ethical dimension, qualifying them for the analysis, conception, development and management of research projects of computer solutions of application in the services related to the Information and Knowledge Society.

01/10/2018 - 15/07/2021 - Murcia, Spain

Computer science

Universidad Católica de San Antonio de Murcia

Data structures and algorithms, systems, architecture, software engineering, and theory of computation.

The most **relevant occupations** or **jobs** are the following:

App programmer.

Web developer or designer.

Database or network and systems administrator.

Computer systems or functional analyst.

Software architect.

IT installation project manager.

Mobile app developer.

Information technology trainer.

Support technician.

Usability expert.

IT consultant.

SEO specialist.

IT auditor.

Field(s) of study

Computer Science

9.305

22/09/2016 - 12/06/2018 - Murcia, Spain

Web app developer/designer

IES José Planes

General Competence with regard to: Developing, implementing and maintaining web applications, irrespective of the model used and using specific technologies, guaranteeing secure access to data and complying with the accessibility, usability and quality criteria required by established standards.

Languages learned: PHP, Java, JavaScript, MySQL, CSS, HTML/XHTML, XML.

Frameworks/libraries used: jQuery, Ajax, Reactjs, Nodejs, Symfony & Doctrine2, Bootstrap, Ruby, SASS, Compass.

The most **relevant occupations** or **jobs** are the following:

Web developer.

Web programmer.

Person in charge of developing web environment applications.

8.8

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Spanish

OTHER LANGUAGE(S):

English

Listening Reading Spoken Spoken Writing
B2 B2 production interaction B2
B2 B2 B2

COMMUNICATION AND INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Communication and interpersonal skills

- Able to help partners solving their problems and giving my point of view.
- Expressing and communicating, with my own ideas.
- Work under pressure.
- Able to manage myself when there is a lot of work to do.

JOB-RELATED SKILLS

Job-related skills

- Good sense of designing.
- Knowledge of keyboard shortcuts.
- CMD programming knowledge.
- Focused on coding as clean as possible.
- Standard use of Photoshop.
- Always looking for new challenges.

Thank you for your time and for reading this document. Sincerely, Nicolas Meseguer.

Murcia, Spain, 20/08/2021

Nicolás Meseguer Iborra